[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "Somebody",
        "back": "Кто-то"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "once",
        "back": "однажды"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "told",
        "back": "сказал"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "me",
        "back": "мне"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "the world",
        "back": "мир"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "is",
        "back": "am, is, are - три рубашки глагола-короля"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "gonna",
        "back": "собирается"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "roll",
        "back": "раздавить"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "setId": 1,
        "front": "me",
        "back": "меня"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "setId": 2,
        "front": "Raid",
        "back": "Поход"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "setId": 2,
        "front": "Shadow",
        "back": "Тени"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "setId": 2,
        "front": "Legends",
        "back": "Легенды"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "setId": 3,
        "front": "Spoon",
        "back": "Ложка"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "setId": 3,
        "front": "Fork",
        "back": "Вилка"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "setId": 3,
        "front": "Knife",
        "back": "Нож"
    }
]